# IJA Project

## Graphical block editor for basic complex number operations.



***Autors***: Matúš Liščinský xlisci02, Tomáš Zubrik xzubri00


Block Editor for computing basic complex number operations with user 
friendly and simple GUI. 


***Controls*** :
Choose the block on the left side with operation you want, click on the scene 
and block will appear. Add to the scene how many blocks you wish and connect them with lines. 
To connect two blocks you have to switch mode by clicking on button with line in toolbar. 
Toolbar also includes buttons for moving with blocks, removing them, removing connections, 
running the scheme and stepping the calculation. Before the calculation itself, 
you will be asked for required, undefined values.  



